<Items>
  <Item ItemID="1046741054">
    <Name>VINTAGE LTHR JACKET/BROWN WHITE STITCH EMO</Name>
    <Category>Clothing &amp; Accessories</Category>
    <Category>Men</Category>
    <Category>Clothing: Regular</Category>
    <Category>Outerwear</Category>
    <Category>Jackets</Category>
    <Category>Leather</Category>
    <Currently>$19.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location>Winnipeg, Manitioba</Location>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:09:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:09:02</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1051" UserID="jordanv@mts.net" />
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#000000; background-color : #AFB8DF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #000000; } VINTAGE LTHR JACKET/BROWN WHITE STITCH EMO This is one cool vintage coat.The color is brown with white stitching,shows good in photo.The jacket is in great condition,shows light wear on brass snap buttons.It's clean and ready to wear .Make is Le Girard and the tag shows no size .The jacket measures as follows Chest is 36'' around,Between shoulders is 17'' Arm inseam is 18'' and outseam is 24'' total length from back of collar is 27''Add 8.00 shipping I WILL COMBINE SHIPPING ON MORE THAN 1 ITEM. I ACCEPT PAYPAL, BILLPOINT, PERSONAL CHECKS AND MONEY ORDERS. I AM LOCATED IN CANADA AND IN ORDER TO KEEP SHIPPING COST REASONABLE I SHIP SURFACE POST. THIS CAN TAKE UP APPROXIMATELY 2 WEEK FOR SMALL ITEMS AND APPROXIMATELY 2- 4 WEEKS FOR LARGE ITEMS (OVER 2.2 POUNDS BOXED). IF YOU DO NOT HAVE THE PATIENCE TO WAIT THIS LONG I WILL SHIP AIR AT THE BUYERS EXPENSE. IF NEITHER OF THESE OPTIONS WILL WORK FOR YOU PLEASE DO NOT BID. Additional Information Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046741911">
    <Name>THE THING Bust ----- #361 ----- BOWEN low low</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Figurines</Category>
    <Currently>$39.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$39.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="25.558428" Longitude="-80.458168">Miami Lakes</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:12:07</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:12:07</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="678" UserID="fantasyville.com" />
    <Description>THE THING #361 ALWAYS LOW! ComicStatues.co ITEM DESCRIPTION: ComicStatues. low numbered exclusive !! Available in December. Sculpted by Randy Bowen. YOU ARE BIDDING FOR 1 BUST TOTAL !! Based on designs of MARVEL COMICS . BOWEN's busts are getting better and better. The Thing stands at 5" tall. PAYMENT &amp; SECURITY: High bidders must contact us WITHIN 48 HOURS AFTER END OF AUCTION by e-mail. All payments must be received 7-10 days after auction end. We accept U.S. BANK MONEY ORDERS, U.S. POSTAL MONEY ORDERS, PERSONAL CHECKS, BUSINESS CHECKS DRAWN ON U.S. FUNDS, BID PAY AND PAYPAL. Bidders with negative feedback are subject to having bid revoked. Please contact us if you have negative feedback. ALWAYS ASK WHAT SHIPPING METHOD YOU ARE GETTING AND WHAT IT INCLUDES. WE ARE VERIFIED SECURE BUSINESS PAYPAL ACCOUNT SO YOUR PURCHASE IS SAFE. UNVERIFIED sellers equals unsecure purchases. Always ask if seller is verified. SHIPPING: We only ship insured w/certified receipt in the USA. Cost in continental U.S. is $9 Canada is $17 and insurance/confirmation is up to the buyer here since it's more costly. If you're an international bidder, please inquire for s/h charges. E-mail me if you have any questions at: danny@ComicStatues.com (305) 826-4664 Visit the home of the GUARANTEED LOW &amp; SAME NUMBERED BUST SELLER FOR BOWEN BUSTS TRANSFORMERS BUSTS DYNAMIC FORCES ALEX ROSS *MARVEL* BUSTS TOMB RAIDER BUST MOORE BUSTS X-MEN MAQUETTES That's right...Only found with us. Check out our other auctions Click on the pic.. Thanks and happy bidding!! You can pay with a MC/Visa here at: I accept PayPal payments! Now Available for International Users I accept US &amp; International bidders &amp; payment with a major credit card via B id P ay . Fast, easy &amp; secure. www.BidPay.com Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Visit ComicStatues.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions All items ship insured/tracked within the USA. It is up to buyer to claim insurance if dam</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046743322">
    <Name>JOSEF Original Lipstick Holder MIB Cute</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Josef</Category>
    <Currently>$8.00</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$38.05</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$8.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="33.942289" Longitude="-118.12901">California</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:15:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:15:45</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="3266" UserID="gsimas1@aol.com" />
    <Description>This is a new JOSEF LIPSTICK HOLDER, it is mint in the box. Doll stands 5 inches tall, and has 3 places to hold your Lipstick around the bottom of her skirt. Her dress is apricot colored, As always it is trimmed with 24 K gold, has paper tag, great item. Buyer pays shipping.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046743772">
    <Name>~* Vintage WHITE Roll Top BREAD BOX sHabBy *~</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bread Boxes</Category>
    <Currently>$27.56</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$38.05</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>4</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="262" UserID="tykon">
          <Location>MN</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 12:16:39</Time>
        <Amount>$14.38</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="244" UserID="mansorama">
          <Location>Sydney,NSW</Location>
          <Country>Australia</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 12:16:39</Time>
        <Amount>$18.78</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="245" UserID="Calvin" />
        <Time>Dec-13-01 12:16:39</Time>
        <Amount>$23.17</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="305" UserID="bodawns">
          <Location>Syracuse Orange Sports</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 12:16:39</Time>
        <Amount>$27.56</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Western MI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:16:39</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:16:39</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1195" UserID="the_estate_collection" />
    <Description>~* Vintage WHITE Roll Top BREAD BOX sHabBy *~ In times like these, when Home and Family mean even more, surround yourself with the things you love. Feast your eyes on this Vintage WHITE Roll Top Aluminum BREAD BOX . This treasure measures 17-1/2" wide by 10-1/2" deep by 7" high. Rolling lid works smoothly. Some very slight marks add to the Character. Buy and Enjoy or would make a great gift. TheEstateCollection.com ~~ NO RESERVE ~~ Thanks for looking and have a great day. Please click here to view Gallery Photos of all Items we have on the Auction. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046744008">
    <Name>Americana Stoneware Double Star Dishes</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$4.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="38.267466" Longitude="-122.658097">Petaluma, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:17:18</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-20-01 12:17:18</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="81" UserID="hausfortuna" />
    <Description>The Haus Fortuna difference Distinctive and artistic accents for the home, one of kind accessories, sensational baby and children's items, unique art objects, exquisite jewelry, and gift sets for any ocassion. Haus Fortuna represents a company that customers can trust for quality merchandise from around the world, exclusive on line values, and excellent customer service. A virtual shoping mall that never closes. Americana Stoneware Double Star Dishes These attractive dishes are the perfect accent to highlight any meal or snack. Will fit with any kitchen d! These lovely BRAND NEW handcrafted dishes will also make a perfect gift! 6" long x 3.5" wide Payment Terms Buyer to prepay $5.35 for shipping and insurance costs. For all shipments outside the Continental U.S. the shipping costs will be assessed after the winner bidder submits shipping address. Payment may be made by cashier's check, money order, personal check, Billpoint, or PayPal. Please allow ten (10) days for personal checks to clear the bank before shipping. High bidder must contact seller within 48 hours after the close of auction for payment arrangements. Payment is due within seven (7) days of auction close . If payment is not received within fifteen (15) days of auction close, Buyer forfeits all rights to purchase and Seller reserves the right to relist the item for sale. Auction Wizard 2000 - The Complete Auction Management Software Solution</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046744653">
    <Name>BAPTIST CHURCH RICHWOOD WEST VIRGINA</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Autographs, Paper &amp; Writing</Category>
    <Category>Paper</Category>
    <Category>Postcards</Category>
    <Category>US State, Town Views</Category>
    <Category>West Virginia</Category>
    <Currently>$1.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="199" UserID="freedom.in.christ">
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 21:14:22</Time>
        <Amount>$1.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>44319</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:19:09</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-20-01 12:19:09</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="305" UserID="slymer1" />
    <Description>CARD IS IN EXCELLENT CONDITION WAS SENT IN 1918 BUYER PAYS 1.50 S &amp; H Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046744794">
    <Name>Felix the Cat Chevrolet pinback pin OLD LOOK</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Pinbacks</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="37" UserID="vsstore7">
          <Location>Waltham, MA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:19:59</Time>
        <Amount>$4.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location Latitude="33.92018" Longitude="-118.14291">California</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:19:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:19:59</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1671" UserID="pvp33" />
    <Description />
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046744876">
    <Name>HUGE OLD 2X4 FT LONG INDIANAPOLIS COLTS FLAG</Name>
    <Category>Sports</Category>
    <Category>Memorabilia</Category>
    <Category>Football-Other</Category>
    <Currently>$16.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$16.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location>PLEASE SEE MY OTHER RELATED AUCTIONS ........</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:19:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:19:34</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="6937" UserID="bschm59102@aol.com" />
    <Description>THIS IS A DISCONTINUED MINT CONDITION NEVER OPENED COLTS HUGE VERTICAL NYLON FLAG!!! THESE ARE GREAT WITH VIBRANT BRIGHT COLORS AND GRAPHICS!!! I HAVE ALL THE TEAMS AVAILABLE IN THESE, IF INTERESTED IN OTHERS JUST LET ME KNOW IF I CAN HELP, THANKS,,,, 27" X 41" LONG!!! $4.00 SHIPPING.. EMAIL ME WITH QUESTIONS PLEASE SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS... Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046746803">
    <Name>Adorable Pair of Mouse Bells</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Metalware</Category>
    <Category>Brass</Category>
    <Currently>$4.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="37.571581" Longitude="-122.0509">Northern Ca</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:24:16</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:24:16</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1269" UserID="vacaglass" />
    <Description>Adorable Pair of Mouse Bells. 4 1/2" tall and 2 1/2" wide at the base. Very good condition. We have purchased over 3000 bells at an estate sale and will be listing them over the next several months. Please keep checking our auctions for the many different types that we will be offering. High Bidder is to pay $0 free for shipping in the USA and insurance above request. Insurance up to $50.00 - $1.10 and 50.01 to $100.00 - 2.00.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046747075">
    <Name>20 different issues of Spawn comics</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Collections</Category>
    <Currently>$8.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$8.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location>N.J.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:24:17</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:24:17</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="307" UserID="jbtc69a@prodigy.com" />
    <Description>20 different issues of Spawn. These books are store stock that have been in storage for a few years. They have not been read or overhandled, some books may even be bagged and boarded already. Be sure to check my other auctions for more lots. I do combine lots to save on shipping. Shipping will be an average of $6-7 per lot shipped within the USA. Insurance and other postal services available on request. I accept checks or money orders. Please have payment submitted within a 2 week period. Any questions you may have please address them early on in the auction. Thanks and good luck !!! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046747948">
    <Name>New Unique Handmade Crochet Tablecloth!!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Textiles</Category>
    <Category>Table Linens</Category>
    <Category>Tablecloths</Category>
    <Currently>$1.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="2946" UserID="oredukman@aol.com">
          <Location>ducktown oregon</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:26:15</Time>
        <Amount>$1.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>la crescenta</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:26:15</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:26:15</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="23" UserID="www_lartisana_com" />
    <Description>TABLECLOTH Ecru 36" Square The Finest Handmade Crochet, 100% Cotton__ YOU ARE BIDDING ON__ THE BEIGE COLOR 36" SQUARE !!!!! This Beautiful Crochet tablecloth is of the finest quality. I am a direct importer of many tablecloths and linens, but the Crochet I carry is by far the best seller in the U.S. . All previous customers praise my products and there is a reason for that. My products are individually examined and are quality assured.__ I started selling linens out of my house and have turned it into a vast collection of the world's finest linens ( email for online catalog ).__ All linens in the Lartisana Collection are handmade giving them a sense of meaning and beauty. I carry all the different sizes to fit any table. I keep a pretty heavy inventory and offer various colors and sizes along with their matching napkins. I will work with you and make special arrangements. ANY QUESTIONS JUST EMAIL.__ WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE MY SITE JUST EMAIL.__ :) Happy Holidays !!!!!!!____ For this great month of December I have listed all the colors and sizes available At the Lowest Possible Prices in the Crochet style 869 in my ebay store !__ Low Prices will remain valid through December !!!!! the 1st customer of every five sales will get to choose a free gift valued at $18 on my site!! example: 1st, 6th, 11th, 16th ...____ click seller's other auctions To See the Following : __ STYLE 869. CROCHET TABLECLOTHS white. 72". Round__ ecru. 72". Round white. 90".Round ecru. 90".Round white. 72x90. oblong/oval__ ecru. 72x90. oblong/oval white. 72x108. oblong/oval ecru. 72x108. oblong/oval white. 72x126. oblong ecru. 72x126. oblong white. 72x144. oblong ecru. 72x144. oblong __18"sq. Matching Napkins. white/ecru STYLE 869. CROCHET TOPPERS white.30".Round/Square ecru.30".Round/Square white.36".Round/Square ecru.36".Round/Square white.45".Round/Square Ecru.45".Round/Square white.54".Round/Square ecru.54".Round/Square Over the years I have put together a collection of Linens from all over the world !!! From tons of toppers / tablecloths / napkins / tapestries / pillow cases / doilies / placemats / runners / tons for the holiday / you name it I got it !!!!!__ Email me for any questions,__ even for opinions. I would love to hear from you!!!!! http://www.lartisana.com/mainsite/tableclothlinks/869 tablecloth.html Napkins are sold separately by the dozen email me for special arrangements__ Please feel free to Email me for any questions that you might have. __I would be more than honored to help and assist you with any of your questions.__ __ Winner pays shipping cost. If you have any questions please email me</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046748095">
    <Name>Cast Iron Nautical Ship Anchor Double Hook</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Metalware</Category>
    <Category>Cast Iron</Category>
    <Currently>$9.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="39.741865" Longitude="-80.07999">Central PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:26:39</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 12:26:39</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1403" UserID="bbbiris@aol.com" />
    <Description>This is a wonderful decorating item to compliment the nautical theme. Cast iron anchor hook measures approx. 5-3/4"h x 4-1/2"w. Buyer to pay $4.35 for priority/confirmed shipping. Insurance is extra. PA residents to include 6% sales tax. Personal check or money order within 10 days of auction close. Personal checks must clear before shipping. Visa/MasterCard accepted through Paypal.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046748106">
    <Name>THE SECOND LIFE OF DOCTOR MIRAGE #1-#7 RUN</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="41.365709" Longitude="-72.927507">WATERBURY,CT.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:32:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-17-01 12:32:19</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="2189" UserID="cabanaman" />
    <Description>THE SECOND LIFE OF DOCTOR MIRAGE #1-#7 RUN THE SECOND LIFE OF DOCTOR MIRAGE #1-#7 RUN (VALIANT COMICS;1991). THIS IS NOT A FULL RUN BUT IS A GREAT START IF YOU WANT TO PUT ONE TOGETHER. ALL STORIES BY BOB LAYTON AND ART BY BERNARD CHANG. ALL 7 ISSUES ARE IN "MINT" CONDITION. SHIPPING IS $2.50 FOR REGULAR MAIL,INTERNATIONAL WILL HAVE TO CHECK. CHECK OUT MY OTHER COMIC MINI-SERIES OR FULL RUN AUCTIONS. We accept Money Orders,Personal Checks,Mastercard,Visa and Discover and Pay Pal. I only accept checks from U.S. banks. Payment must be received within 10 days after the close of the auction. With money orders, we ship as soon as we receive your payment. Personal Checks take 2 weeks to clear. Buyer pays exact shipping. International orders will have to check shipping and pay in U.S.Funds only. If you have any questions, please ask them before you make your bid. GOOD LUCK!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046750204">
    <Name>FRESH PAINT NE VILL SIGN NO RESERVE VISA/MC</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>New England Village</Category>
    <Currently>$15.90</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$15.90</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="43.430275" Longitude="-96.1663">rock rapids, ia</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:29:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 12:29:59</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="7301" UserID="jrcoll@rconnect.com" />
    <Description>NEW ENGLAND VILLAGE " FRESH PAINT" NE VILL SIGN #56592. MIB. NO RESERVE. S/H $4.50. SEE OTHER LISTINGS FOR REDUCED SHIPPING. PAYMENT WITHIN 10 DAYS OF AUCTION. CHECKS MUST CLEAR. GOOD LUCK BIDDING!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1046750805">
    <Name>LOOKOUT TOWER ORN RET 98 NO RESERVE VISA/MC</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>North Pole</Category>
    <Currently>$9.90</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.90</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="43.430275" Longitude="-96.1663">rock rapids, ia</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-10-01 12:30:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 12:30:59</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="7301" UserID="jrcoll@rconnect.com" />
    <Description>NORTH POLE LOOKOUT TOWER ORNAMENT #98742. RETIRED 1998. NON-LIGHTED. MINT IN BOX. NO RESERVE. S/H $4.50. SEE OTHER LISTINGS FOR REDUCED SHIPPING. PAYMENT WITHIN 10 DAYS OF AUCTION. CHECKS MUST CLEAR. GOOD LUCK BIDDING!</Description>
  </Item>
</Items>